Wow!
Yes!
That's great!
That's amazing!
It's a transformer!
Aah!
Wow!
It's so cute!
The rotation is so beautiful!
Yes!
There you go.
I think it's going to arrive.
Oh, yeah!
That's great. That's great.
Fifty centimeters to go.
50 more centimeters.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Ah!
Nice ball!
Nice.
Here we go.
Here you go.
Come on in Maj Ir 321
wipe
Ohhhhhh!
Thank you for watching!
Yes, just the right pickin' oharu and snacks oharu.
OHFURA!!!!!!!
Yes, those of you who are a little curious,
This is Sand Sauce Daiki.
Yes, for those of you who have a wide green on your agency seat, this is Rui Yoshikawa. Yes, the person with the wide green on the Agency seat is Rui Yoshikawa.
Yes, first of all, thank you for your greeting.
Now, on behalf of the group, I would like to talk to Ms. Kanami Tsujino, the general manager of the group.
First of all, what are your impressions of the Izumo Spinkate grounds and stadium?
The head of the group is a lot of people come out to Izumo Spinkuate,
I think it is pink and dyed pink, flowery and cute and cutesy.
Cute, that is also the normal atmosphere.
Yes, it is.
In that atmosphere, later today, Ms. Tsujino will throw out the first pitch before the game,
How did you feel when you were chosen to throw out the first pitch?
I was really happy, and my mother was a high school student,
I was even happier when I became a high school student and played the game in this way.
I was even more happy to see people who came to the tournament today, such as those who came to the tournament via my mother's delivery,
I want to do my best.
It seems that you have a lot of thoughts in your mind, but could you tell us again one more character for the first pitch?
Yes, I have been practicing a lot. I have practiced a lot,
I've been practicing a lot, so I'm going to do my best to deliver at the end of the practice session.
You are very enthusiastic. Thank you very much.
And after this, we are planning to release on Wednesday, May 29th, TikTok, etc,
We will be performing a popular song on social networking sites, the cutest of the cutest.
What is this song about?
Yes, it is a song that is popular on social networking sites such as TikTok. This song is about being cute at the highest level,
I could be cute in the genre that you are looking at me.
It features the lyrics, “Nice to meet you, thank you,” and is a super-positive duo.
Since the social networking site is TikTok, there might be some of you who have heard of this song,
If so, we would be very happy if you could dance with us. I would be very happy if you could dance with us.
I am looking forward to seeing you all.
Last but not least, a message to Fukuoka, Yamato, Oki, and all ZUFANS,
Please give me a message.
Yes, I have a message for all the Zufans. Today, I hope that Forks can win,
I would like to perform at our college.
Let's have fun even if you are watching with us. Best regards.
Yes, let's all have fun together. Thank you very much.
Okay, now two times, the cutest of the cutest!
Thank you for watching.
You might be lucky.
I'm the one with the rules. I'm the one who rules.
You're so cute right now.
I can't believe you didn't finish when you started.
I can't believe you didn't finish.
Enter National.
That's no good.
My elves are talking.
Like they always do.
I'd like to see what's underneath.
Someday you're gonna have a hard day.
You'll pull me closer.
You're not doing it to me.
Because I'm doing it to you right now
Hey, you know what the first pretty thing is?
When they say it's just right up there
It's a reversal of my belief that looks don't matter.
Hey, you're the first pretty thing I've ever seen
Suddenly you're pretty when you love someone
Suddenly I'm cute because I love you
I've got love for you, and suddenly you're cute
My love for you is suddenly adorable
Now then, you long for the heart!
That's all for us, super kimix energy. Thank you very much.
We're filming a new piece...
полностью итан
Hair and face
This hand over here is fine.
So cute.
Very cute.
I love the girls' class.
I've been practicing so much that my muscles are sore even now.
I really want to make a no-brainer!
To the best of my ability
I'm going to show what I can do.
I will do my best!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching! Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
han
mar
ar
Soon там
I'm sorry to hear that
The most perverted bear is Kamaz.
Oh no, I want to do it again
shiuments of shirobuchi
step-by-step
Kirito
Riho
me-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
I don't know why, whenever it rains it seems like I'm crying
Wash away your naughty thoughts, otherwise I can't walk
Come on, let's go wherever you want Goodbye goodbye, I was yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering, my heart is sunny
I'm playing the rainbow piano
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
Please subscribe to our channel!
I don't know why, but when I smile, it's as if the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold.
I'm sure there's someone crying somewhere, just a little bit of me
I want to share it with you
I still don't know the scenery in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
And lead us on the way.
Thank you for watching.
I can tell you now, if you ever wonder why you cried
And when the time comes again, you'll remember. And time will soon remember
So that we can laugh when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
It's as if my heart is in a sunny mood
Rainbow pools of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day
Tears are flowing down my face
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la